[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the Kennedy brothers became known as The Lion of the Senate?", "correct_answer": "Edward M. Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert F. Kennedy", "Joseph P. Kennedy Jr.", "John F. Kennedy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stir frying is a term used to describe two fast Chinese cooking techniques: ch\u01ceo and b\u00e0o.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of object does the term black hole refer to in physics?", "correct_answer": "A collapsed star", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "A space storm", "A gap between time and space"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these are considered the two developers of the modern calculus?", "correct_answer": "Newton and Leibnitz", "incorrect_answers": ["Newton and Gauss", "Euler and Cauchy", "Newton and Euler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He played a tough judge in the Clint Eastwood flick Hangem High in 1968. He was also the businessman with the store of weapons in Stephen Kings Maximum Overdrive.", "correct_answer": "Pat Hingle", "incorrect_answers": ["Wally Cox", "Richard Crenna", "Dan Haggerty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of the following tubes is the blood to additive ratio most critical?", "correct_answer": "Light Blue stopper", "incorrect_answers": ["Lavender Stopper", "Green Stopper", "Red Stopper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I killed a helicopter with a car. Who am I?", "correct_answer": "John McClane", "incorrect_answers": ["Indiana Jones", "Rambo", "The Terminator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "King John Sobieski of Poland saved Vienna from Ottoman invaders. In his honor something new was invented.  What was it ?", "correct_answer": "The bagel", "incorrect_answers": ["The Polish saddle", "The  epee", "Heeled boots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first State of the Union Address attributed to?", "correct_answer": "George Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Jefferson Thomas", "John Adams", "James Madison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Former NBA coach Frank Layton once fined small forward Adrian Dantley thirty pieces of silver.  What did Layton say the fine was for?", "correct_answer": "Betrayal", "incorrect_answers": ["Being late to three  practices in a row", "Asking to be traded", "Missing three foul shots in a row"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other common name is used for the Kittis Hog-nosed Bat, the smallest bat species in the world?", "correct_answer": "Bumblebee bat", "incorrect_answers": ["Wasp bat", "Hummingbird bat", "Ladybug bat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word does Bruce Almighty use as an exclamation when he feels happy or ironically when he feels taken in?", "correct_answer": "Beautiful!", "incorrect_answers": ["Wonderful!", "Marvelous!", "Sweet!"]}]